http://www.ffin.com/en-us/about/terms-of-use/

First Financial Bank Terms of Use
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE:Welcome to the First Financial Bankshares, Inc. web site. First Financial Bankshares and its affiliates (“First Financial”, “Bank” or “Institution”) provide access to its web site (the “Site”) and its products and services to you subject to the following Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Terms”). By accessing the Site, you consent to and accept the Terms and any amendments to the Terms. First Financial may revise the Terms at any time, without giving you prior notice, by updating this posting. You can review the most current version of the Terms at any time at: https://www.ffin.com or through other notice to you. In addition, once you have registered for any First Financial service or services (the “Service(s)”) available through the Site, you and First Financial shall be subject to the applicable agreement (“Service Agreements”) that you agree to at the time of registration for the service. You agree to review the Terms regularly, and your continued access or use of the Site will mean that you agree to any changes. USE OF SITE In order to access the Site, you must obtain access to the Internet by subscribing to an Internet Service Provider (“ISP”) of your choice and by using compatible hardware, software, and web browser. You are solely responsible for any fees associated with your access to the Internet, including the fees of your ISP. To protect the security of your personal account information, First Financial requires you to use a web browser that supports adequate security measures including the use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology, as determined from time to time by the Bank. At the time you access a Service where personal account information is available, First Financial will advise you if you do not have a currently acceptable web browser version and will provide you the opportunity to upgrade your version. You are responsible at your expense for the procurement, installation, maintenance, and operation of any necessary equipment to access the Site. The Bank is not responsible for any errors or failures of your equipment. As with all uses of the Internet, you should use anti-virus and anti-malware software when accessing the Site. Bank is not responsible for any electronic virus that you may encounter using the online services. You confirm that you have investigated our Online Security Procedures and that you have instituted the proper controls for access to Online Services from your computers, mobile devices and terminals. You confirm that the security system and controls are commercially reasonable for your business and appropriate for your personal accounts. You agree that you are responsible for the performance and protection of any browser or operating system used in connection with the Site, including the prompt adoption of all security patches, installing and mainlining up to date any malicious code security (“antivirus”) and other security measures issued or recommended from time to time by the suppliers of such software. We encourage you to scan your computer, mobile devices and removable storage routinely using a reliable virus protection product to detect and remove viruses. If undetected and unrepaired, a virus can corrupt and destroy your programs, files, and hardware. The Bank is not responsible for any computer virus or related problems that may be associated with your use of the Site or any of the Service(s). All products and services of First Financial are subject to the terms and conditions of the applicable Service Agreements governing their use. Product offers, rates, terms, and other information provided are subject to change without notice. First Financial restricts access to Password-protected areas of the Site to authorized users only. If you are an authorized user, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your User ID, your Password and for any Additional Authentication Information (AAI) that First Financial may require you to enter for security and authentication purposes. For all transactions you conduct as an authorized user, you must use your User ID and Password, and from time-to-time you may be asked to enter your AAI for additional security purposes or procedures. You agree to immediately notify First Financial of any unauthorized use of your User ID, your Password and/or your AAI, or any other breach of security. For security reasons, you should not leave your computer unattended while using the Services and you should always log out of the Site after using the Services. First Financial is not liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to protect the confidentiality of your User ID, Password and/or AAI, or your other security lapses. CHILDREN USING OUR SITE AND OUR SERVICES The safety of children is very important to First Financial. Children should always ask a parent or legal guardian for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. First Financial is a general audience Site, and we expect that children may visit our Site. Only the parent or legal guardian of a child under the age of 13 can access our Services, even when a deposit account has been established on behalf of the child. Should you have additional questions or concerns, please contact our Customer Service Center at 1-888-588-2623, Monday through Friday 8:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m. and on Saturdays from 8:00 a.m. to 7:00 p.m. CST/CDT. PRIVACY POLICY First Financial reserves the right to place various “cookies” or similar text files on your computer to record preferences you have entered and to modify the Site accordingly, and also for security or user authentication purposes. For information regarding First Financial’s privacy policy and use of cookies, please see the Privacy Statement. The privacy policies of other businesses providing any of the services and products on the Site may be different than those of First Financial and you should review those policies before engaging in a transaction or providing any personally identifying information to such businesses. COMMUNICATIONS All communications or other materials transmitted to First Financial through this Site are not confidential and are deemed to be First Financial’s property. The communications or other materials may be used for any purpose within the limits of our Customer Privacy Statement. Electronic mail (“e-mail”) communication over the Internet is not confidential or secure. First Financial is not responsible for any damages in connection with an e-mail you send to First Financial or an e-mail First Financial sends to you at your request. If you register for a Service, you agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself, if prompted by the Service’s registration form, and to maintain and promptly update the registration data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. First Financial reserves the right to verify any personal information you provide and the right to make inquiries about you to the extent allowed in our Customer Privacy Statement with regard to a request by you or a co-signer for a product, service, or customer assistance. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or First Financial has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, First Financial has the right to suspend or terminate your access to the Site and refuse any and all current or future use of the Services (or any portion thereof). COPYRIGHT/TRADEMARKS This Site is owned and operated by First Financial, or others as indicated. All of the material displayed on this Site, including the images, design, look and feel, photographs, audio, page headers, software, buttons, video, other icons, graphics, text, screens, and web pages and the selection and arrangement thereof (“Content”) is either the property of First Financial or is displayed by way of a license from the material’s owner. First Financial, or others as indicated, also owns the trademarks, service marks, registered service marks, or registered trademarks and logos (“Marks”) displayed on the Site. You agree not to use the Content or Marks for any purpose without the express written consent of First Financial or the third party that may own the Content or Marks. BOOKMARKING AND LINKING You understand that you may create a bookmark in your web browser to the First Financial home page. You may not create any link to either the First Financial home page or any other of the Bank’s web site pages without the written approval of First Financial, including, without limitation, a link on a publicly accessible website. You may not use any of First Financial’s Marks or Content. No person may link to this Site from any website not owned or sponsored by First Financial without first notifying First Financial of the intention to create such link and obtaining First Financial’s written permission. No web site linking to this Site may frame or border this Site with the content of the linking site visible in the same window without First Financial’s express written permission. Any use of materials on this Site without the prior written consent of First Financial other than as expressly set out herein is prohibited. THIRD PARTY CONTENT, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES First Financial Bank is not responsible for the content, products, or services provided on third-party sites hyperlinked from this page. First Financial Bank does not endorse or guarantee the products, information, or recommendations provided on third party sites hyperlinked from this page, and First Financial Bank is not liable for the failure of products or services offered on those third party sites. Third party sites may provide less information privacy or security than First Financial Bank web sites. You should review the privacy and security policies of a website before you provide personal or confidential information. NO WARRANTIES FIRST FINANCIAL PROVIDES THE SITE, ALL CONTENT AND THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES OFFERED FOR SALE ON THE SITE TO YOU “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. FIRST FINANCIAL BANK DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL SUCH REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW INCLUDING THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, SECURITY, ACCURACY, ACCESSIBILITY, NON-INTERRUPTION AND NONINFRINGEMENT. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. THIS WARRANTY GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM STATE TO STATE. EXCLUSION OF DAMAGES; LIMITATION ON LIABILITY TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, FIRST FINANCIAL SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR OTHERS FOR ANY DIRECT, COMPENSATORY, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, CONSEQUENTIAL OR OTHER DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE TERMS, THE SITE OR THE SERVICES, EVEN IF FIRST FINANCIAL HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IF, NOTWITHSTANDING THE OTHER PROVISIONS OF THE TERMS, FIRST FINANCIAL SHOULD HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE TERMS, THE SITE OR THE SERVICES, YOU AGREE SUCH LIABILITY SHALL NOT EXCEED $1,000. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. THIS CLAUSE GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM STATE TO STATE. INDEMNIFICATION TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, YOU AGREE TO RELEASE, INDEMNIFY, DEFEND AND HOLD HARMLESS FIRST FINANCIAL AND ITS OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, DIRECTORS, SUPPLIERS AND AGENTS, IN THEIR INDIVIDUAL CAPACITIES OR OTHERWISE, FROM AND AGAINST ALL DAMAGES,CLAIMS, LIABILITIES AND EXPENSES (INCLUDING ATTORNEYS’ FEES) BROUGHT BY ANY PERSON ARISING FROM OR RELATING TO YOUR ACCESS AND USE OF THE SITE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY CLAIMS ALLEGING FACTS THAT IF TRUE WOULD CONSTITUTE A BREACH BY USER OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. LAWS AND REGULATIONS The Terms constitute the entire agreement between you and First Financial with respect to your access to the Site and governs your use of the Site, superseding any prior agreements between you and First Financial. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Authorized users may be subject to additional terms and conditions as set forth in any other applicable Bank online services agreement. You agree that Texas law, without regard to conflicts of law principles, shall govern your access to and use of this Site, except to the extent such laws are preempted by federal law or regulation. You and First Financial agree, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the state or federal courts located within Taylor County, Texas and to venue in Abilene, Texas. Unless otherwise specified, this Site is controlled and operated by First Financial from its offices within the state of Texas. First Financial makes no representation that materials in the Site or the Services are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Those who choose to access this Site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. First Financial reserves the right to seek all remedies available at law and in equity for violations of these terms and conditions, including the right to block access from a particular Internet address to the Site. This Site is intended for use only in the United States or other jurisdiction that would recognize the choice of law and choice of jurisdiction provisions made herein. The failure of First Financial Bank to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of the Terms is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties’ intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of the Terms remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, you must give us notice of any claim or course of action (a “Claim”) arising out of or related to use of the Site within one (1) year after you became aware of the material facts and circumstances giving rise to such Claim and any Claim must be filed within two (2) years after such claim arose or be forever barred.
Personal
Banking
Checking
Debit Cards and Alerts
Managing Your Account
Savings
CDS & IRAS
Online & Mobile Banking
